Ok, so here once again, we're in the fairway bunker.
I've got a shot at the green with my 9 iron here.
So what I'm going to do is I'm going to look at the green, so I'm going to take my line on this ball so I want to get parallel to the line of flight of the ball, however, there is a tendency to fade the ball when you're hitting out of sand.
So, you might want to correct for that but you know your own game.
So I want you to get a good solid stance, be balanced because sand is loose and you don't want to have a bad, when you take the club back you want to be in good balance.
Because bad balance you'll hit a bad shot.
Because the sand is very unforgiving.
So that ball was pretty straight, not quite as far as I'd like.
So let's try one more here.
So when I'm on sand I do kind of move my feet a lot because I'm trying to find that perfect balance.
This isn't like hitting off the nice firm ground.
So I feel pretty comfortable here and I struck that one just right and I should be all over the pin with that one.
So this shot looks harder than it is but don't get discouraged.
If you practice your fairway sand shots it's going to have a great effect on your hitting the ball off the grass also.
Because, if you can hit out of this consistently hitting off the grass is easy.